Guide to the Duke University Progress Pictures Collection, 1925-1932 UA.01.15.0012
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- West Campus, 1927-1932
  - West Campus Progress Picture #77, 1928 May 30 (Box 2, Print WC77)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Quadrangle near the front of Class Room and Auditorium, showing Union Building below first floor, with Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] in upper right hand part of picture." [Dated 1928-05-31 on back of photo]
  - West Campus Progress Picture #78, 1928 May 30 (Box 2, Print WC78)
    From back of photo: "Taken from near the rear of Union Building. Showing Union Building on left and end of Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] on right." [Dated 1928-05-31 on back of photo]
  - West Campus Progress Picture #79, 1928 June 18 (Box 2, Print WC79)
    From back of photo: "View of the Quarry near Hillsborough showing method of operation."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #80, 1928 June 18 (Box 2, Print WC80)
    From back of photo: "View of the Quarry near Hillsboro [Hillsborough] showing close up view of rock face."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #81, 1928 June 18 (Box 2, Print WC81)
    From back of photo: "View of the Quarry near Hillsboro [Hillsborough] showing rock before same is loosened with dynamite."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #82, 1928 June 18 (Box 2, Print WC82)
    From back of photo: "View of the Quarry near Hillsboro [Hillsborough] showing rock being loaded on cars. Also on the right of the picture is shown waste material from quarry."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #83, 1928 June 5; 19.4 cm x 24.8 cm (Box 2, Print WC83)
    Photo shows the ceremony for laying cornerstone for the Union Building. Doris Duke, James B. Duke's only child, set the cornerstone.
  - West Campus Progress Picture #84, 1928 June 5; 19.4 cm x 24.8 cm (Box 2, Print WC84)
    Photo shows the ceremony for laying cornerstone for the Union Building.
  - West Campus Progress Picture #85, 1928 June 5; 19.4 cm x 24.8 cm (Box 2, Print WC85)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #86, 1928 June 5; 19.4 cm x 24.8 cm (Box 2, Print WC86)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #87, 1928 June 5; 19.4 cm x 24.8 cm (Box 2, Print WC87)
    Photo shows the ceremony for laying cornerstone for the Union Building. Group C Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] in background. Gowned figures process in the middle ground.
  - West Campus Progress Picture #88, 1928 June 5; 19.4 cm x 24.8 cm (Box 2, Print WC88)
    Photo shows the ceremony for laying cornerstone for the Union Building. Group C Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] in background.
  - West Campus Progress Picture #89, 1928 July 2 (Box 2, Print WC89)
    From back of photo: "Showing Service Court Entrance at Hospital. All of steel has been erected to Fourth Floor, and roof steel completed on wing of building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #90, 1928 July 2 (Box 2, Print WC90)
    From back of photo: "View showing steel on Hospital part of building erected to Fourth Floor. No steel has been set on Medical School."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #91, 1928 July 2 (Box 2, Print WC91)
    From back of photo: "Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] showing entrance to Court from large Quadrangle."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #92, 1928 July 2 (Box 2, Print WC92)
    From back of photo: "Showing Union Building taken from near the end of Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #93, 1928 July 2 (Box 2, Print WC93)
    From back of photo: "Showing foundation completed for School of Religion and forms built for concrete foundation for Library."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #94, 1928 July 2 (Box 2, Print WC94)
    From back of photo: "View showing Union Building, taken from near location of Chapel. In foreground to the right is location of Class Room and Auditorium Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #95, 1928 July 2 (Box 2, Print WC95)
    From back of photo: "Showing forms built for concrete foundation for Library."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #96, 1928 July 2 (Box 2, Print WC96)
    From back of photo: "Heating Plant showing construction of Coal Trestle."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #97, 1928 July 2 (Box 2, Print WC97)
    From back of photo: "Heating Plant showing masonry foundation completed ready for steel superstructure."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #98, 1928 August 1 (Box 2, Print WC98)
    From back of photo: "Hospital. View showing Service Entrance to Hospital."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #99, 1928 August 1 (Box 2, Print WC99)
    From back of photo: "View showing steel work on Hospital, also shows foundation for steel of Medical School."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #100, 1928 August 1 (Box 2, Print WC100)
    From back of photo: "View showing concrete foundation of School of Religion and Library completed ready for steel and stone work."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #101, 1928 August 1 (Box 3, Print WC101)
    From back of photo: "View showing Union Building, taken from location of Chapel. This shows stone work almost to second floor of Union Building. On right of picture is location of Class Room and Auditorium Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #102, 1928 August 1 (Box 3, Print WC102)
    From back of photo: "View taken from center of Quadrangle showing front of Union Building. To the left of picture is shown Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #103, 1928 August 1 (Box 3, Print WC103)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Quadrangle near corner of Library showing concrete foundation of Library and foundation of School of Religion. At upper left is shown part of the Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #104, 1928 August 1 (Box 3, Print WC104)
    From back of photo: "View taken from end of Quadrangle showing part of Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #105, 1928 August 1 (Box 3, Print WC105)
    From back of photo: "View showing Heating Plant."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #106, 1928 August 1 (Box 3, Print WC106)
    From back of photo: "View showing Heating Plant. Practically all structural steel is erected, including coal bunkers. Trestle in foreground for unloading and storing coal."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #107, 1928 September 1 (Box 3, Print WC107)
    From back of photo: "View showing elevation of Hospital at Service Entrance."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #108, 1928 September 1 (Box 3, Print WC108)
    From back of photo: "View looking across foundation for Medical School showing Hospital."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #109, 1928 September 1 (Box 3, Print WC109)
    From back of photo: "View taken from near the location of Chapel looking across foundation for School of Religion and Library."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #110, 1928 September 1 (Box 3, Print WC110)
    From back of photo: "View taken from near the location of Chapel, looking across foundation for Class Room and Auditorium, showing Union Building in the background."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #111, 1928 September 1 (Box 3, Print WC111)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Main Quadrangle, looking across foundation of Library and School of Religion, showing location for Chapel in the upper left hand part of the picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #112, 1928 September 1 (Box 3, Print WC112)
    From back of photo: "View taken from near the center of the Main Quadrangles, showing Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #113, 1928 September 1 (Box 3, Print WC113)
    From back of photo: "View taken from the end of Quadrangle showing the end of Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle]. This shows steel work and stone completed ready for roof slab."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #114, 1928 September 1 (Box 3, Print WC114)
    From back of photo: "View showing Heating Plant. All steel work has been erected and brick work started."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #115, 1928 September 1 (Box 3, Print WC115)
    From back of photo: "Showing Heating Plant and foundation for stack."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #116, 1928 October 1 (Box 3, Print WC116)
    From back of photo: "View showing elevation of wing of Hosptial at Service Court Entrance."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #117, 1928 October 1 (Box 3, Print WC117)
    From back of photo: "View showing foundation for Medical School in foreground with Hospital in background. The steel roof on all of the Hospital except the upper left hand corner is completely erected."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #118, 1928 October 1 (Box 3, Print WC118)
    From back of photo: "View showing part of the first floor of Library completed and foundations for School of Religion complete practically to First Floor level."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #119, 1928 October 1 (Box 3, Print WC119)
    From back of photo: "View taken from proposed location of Chapel looking across foundation for School of Religion and Library."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #120, 1928 October 1 (Box 3, Print WC120)
    From back of photo: "View taken from proposed location of Chapel, looking across foundation of Auditorium Building showing Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #121, 1928 October 1 (Box 3, Print WC121)
    From back of photo: "View taken from center of Main Quadrangle showing Union Building"
  - West Campus Progress Picture #122, 1928 October 1 (Box 3, Print WC122)
    From back of photo: "View taken from main Quadrangle showing South end of Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle]. This shows stone work and steel complete ready for gypsum roof slabs. The two brick chimneys shown are complete."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #123, 1928 October 1 (Box 3, Print WC123)
    From back of photo: "View showing Heating Plant with coal trestle completed and all steel erected. Brick stack shown in upper center of the picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #124, 1928 October 1 (Box 3, Print WC124)
    From back of photo: "View showing first two boilers erected."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #125, 1928 October 1 (Box 3, Print WC125)
    From back of photo: "View taken from the location of Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle] showing foundation excavation along Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #126, 1928 November 1 (Box 3, Print WC126)
    From back of photo: "View showing elevation of Hospital at service entrance."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #127, 1928 November 1 (Box 3, Print WC127)
    From back of photo: "View taken from main Quadrangle showing structural steel for Medical School erected to Fourth Floor."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #128, 1928 November 1 (Box 3, Print WC128)
    From back of photo: "View showing foundation for Library and School of Religion."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #129, 1928 November 1 (Box 3, Print WC129)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Main Quadrangle showing Union Building and Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #130, 1928 November 1 (Box 3, Print WC130)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Main Quadrangle showing the end of Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] next to Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle].
  - West Campus Progress Picture #131, 1928 November 1 (Box 3, Print WC131)
    From back of photo: "View taken from near Chapel location showing School of Religion and Library."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #132, 1928 November 1 (Box 3, Print WC132)
    From back of photo: "View taken from near Chapel location showing the foundation for the Auditorium Building and Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #133, 1928 November 1 (Box 3, Print WC133)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #134, 1928 November 1 (Box 3, Print WC134)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #135, 1928 November 1 (Box 3, Print WC135)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Quadrangle showing foundation for Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #136, 1928 November 1 (Box 3, Print WC136)
    From back of photo: "View showing excavation for [Wallace Wade] Stadium."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #137, 1928 December 3 (Box 3, Print WC137)
    From back of photo: "View showing wing of Hospital at the Service Court Entrance, showing all stone work completed and scaffold removed."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #138, 1928 December 3 (Box 3, Print WC138)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Main Quadrangle showing steel erected on end of Medical School. This shows stone work started on this part of the building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #139, 1928 December 3 (Box 3, Print WC139)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Main Quadrangle showing Library stone work up to second floor. Union Building roof steel can be seen at the upper left hand corner of the picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #140, 1928 December 3 (Box 3, Print WC140)
    From back of photo: "View taken from center of Quadrangle showing Union Building. All stone practically completed on this building and all steel except tower completed. Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] shown at left of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #141, 1928 December 3 (Box 3, Print WC141)
    From back of photo: "View showing Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle], taken from Quadrangle."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #142, 1928 December 3 (Box 3, Print WC142)
    From back of photo: "View taken from near Chapel location showing foundation for Class Room and Auditorium Building, and also showing Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #143, 1928 December 3 (Box 3, Print WC143)
    From back of photo: "View taken from near location of Chapel, showing foundation for School of Religion up to first floor, and Library stone work up to second floor."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #144, 1928 December 3 (Box 3, Print WC144)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #145, 1928 December 3 (Box 3, Print WC145)
    From back of photo: "View taken from near Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle] showing concrete foundation completed for Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #146, 1928 December 3 (Box 3, Print WC146)
    From back of photo: "Excavation for [Wallace Wade] Stadium. This picture taken from top of the Players Entrance Tunnel looking South, showing grading on the left side of the Horseshoe very near completed. No excavation has been done on the right side of the Horseshoe."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #147, 1928 December 3 (Box 3, Print WC147)
    From back of photo: "View taken from the open end of the Horseshoe showing excavation on the East side."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #148, 1929 January 7 (Box 3, Print WC148)
    From back of photo: "View showing elevation of the Hospital at the Service Entrance."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #149, 1929 January 7 (Box 3, Print WC149)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Main Quadrangle showing the front of the Medical School."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #150, 1929 January 7 (Box 3, Print WC150)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Main Quadrangle showing Library Building. Union Building at extreme left of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #151, 1929 January 7 (Box 3, Print WC151)
    From back of photo: "View taken from center of Main Quadrangle showing Union Building and Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #152, 1929 January 7 (Box 3, Print WC152)
    From back of photo: "View showing front of Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #153, 1929 January 7 (Box 3, Print WC153)
    From back of photo: "View showing concrete foundation completed for Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle]. Medical School can be seen in upper left hand corner."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #154, 1929 January 7 (Box 3, Print WC154)
    From back of photo: "View taken from near Chapel site showing foundation for Auditorium Building, also Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #155, 1929 January 7 (Box 3, Print WC155)
    From back of photo: "View taken from near Chapel site showing School of Religion and Library Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #156, 1929 January 7 (Box 3, Print WC156)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #157, 1929 January 7 (Box 3, Print WC157)
    From back of photo: "View showing grading for [Wallace Wade] Stadium. Picture taken from center of Horseshoe."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #158, 1929 January 7 (Box 3, Print WC158)
    From back of photo: "View showing grading for [Wallace Wade] Stadium. Picture taken from open end of Horseshoe."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #159, 1929 January 9 (Box 3, Print WC159)
    From back of photo: "Showing detail of roof on one end of Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #160, 1929 January 9 (Box 3, Print WC160)
    From back of photo: "View showing Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #161, 1929 February 4 (Box 3, Print WC161)
    From back of photo: "View showing front of Medical School."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #162, 1929 February 4 (Box 3, Print WC162)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Quadrangle showing foundation for Law Building [now Languages Building]. Library and Union Building at the left."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #163, 1929 February 4 (Box 3, Print WC163)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Quadrangle showing Union Building and Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #164, 1929 February 4 (Box 3, Print WC164)
    From back of photo: "View showing wing of Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #165, 1929 February 4 (Box 3, Print WC165)
    From back of photo: "View showing Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] with foundation for Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle] in the foreground."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #166, 1929 February 4 (Box 3, Print WC166)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Chapel location showing School of Religion and Library Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #167, 1929 February 4 (Box 3, Print WC167)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Chapel location showing Union Building and foundation for Class Room and Auditorium Building at the right of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #168, 1929 February 4 (Box 3, Print WC168)
    From back of photo: "View taken from the rear of Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle] showing foundation for Group 'A' Dormitory. Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] and Union Building at the upper left of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #169, 1929 February 4 (Box 3, Print WC169)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #170, 1929 February 4 (Box 3, Print WC170)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #171, 1929 February 4 (Box 3, Print WC171)
    From back of photo: "View showing excavation for [Wallace Wade] Stadium, taken from open end of Horseshoe."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #172, 1929 February 4 (Box 3, Print WC172)
    From back of photo: "View showing site of [Card] Gymnasium, taken from point near Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle] looking toward [Wallace Wade] Stadium."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #173, 1929 March 1 (Box 3, Print WC173)
    From back of photo: "View showing front of the Medical School."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #174, 1929 March 1 (Box 3, Print WC174)
    From back of photo: "View showing the front of the Library. Union Building at left of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #175, 1929 March 1 (Box 3, Print WC175)
    From back of photo: "View taken from center of Quadrangle showing Union Building and Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle]."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #176, 1929 March 1 (Box 3, Print WC176)
    From back of photo: "View taken from the rear of Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle] showing foundation for Group 'A' Dormitory, with Union Building and Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] in the background."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #177, 1929 March 1 (Box 3, Print WC177)
    From back of photo: "View taken from rear of Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle] showing foundation for Group 'B' Dormitory and showing Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle]. At extreme right center of the picture is shown part of the Medical School Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #178, 1929 March 1 (Box 3, Print WC178)
    From back of photo: "View taken from near Chapel location showing foundation for Class Room and Auditorium Building and also two sides of the Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #179, 1929 March 1 (Box 3, Print WC179)
    From back of photo: "View taken from near Chapel location showing School of Religion and Library Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #180, 1929 March 1 (Box 3, Print WC180)
    From back of photo: "View taken from center of Horseshoe at [Wallace Wade] Stadium showing top of fills on each side completed."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #181, 1929 March 1 (Box 3, Print WC181)
    From back of photo: "View taken from open end of Horseshoe at [Wallace Wade] Stadium, showing top of fills completed."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #182, 1929 March 1 (Box 3, Print WC182)
    From back of photo: "View taken from rear of Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle] showing proposed site of the new [Card] Gymnasium. [Wallace Wade] Stadium can be seen in the background through the woods."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #183, 1929 April 2 (Box 3, Print WC183)
    From back of photo: "View showing the campus front of the Medical School."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #184, 1929 April 2 (Box 3, Print WC184)
    From back of photo: "View taken from campus, showing Library Building in center of picture with Law Building [now Languages Building] on the right and Union Building on the left."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #185, 1929 April 2 (Box 3, Print WC185)
    From back of photo: "View showing campus front of Union Building."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #186, 1929 April 2 (Box 3, Print WC186)
    From back of photo: "View showing Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle], taken from near center of Group 'B' Dormitory [Crowell Quadrangle].
  - West Campus Progress Picture #187, 1929 April 2 (Box 3, Print WC187)
    From back of photo: "View showing foundation for Group 'A' Dormitory [Craven Quadrangle], looking across quadrangle showing Group 'C' Dormitories [Kilgo Quadrangle] and Union Bldg."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #188, 1929 April 2 (Box 3, Print WC188)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Chapel location, showing Union Building and foundation for Auditorium Building built to first floor level."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #189, 1929 April 2 (Box 3, Print WC189)
  - West Campus Progress Picture #190, 1929 April 2 (Box 3, Print WC190)
    From back of photo: "View looking South, showing location for [Card] Gymnasium at road and [Wallace Wade] Stadium beyond trees."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #191, 1929 April 2 (Box 3, Print WC191)
    From back of photo: "View showing grading for [Wallace Wade] Stadium, taken from closed end of Horseshoe."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #192, 1929 April 2 (Box 3, Print WC192)
    From back of photo: "View showing grading for [Wallace Wade] Stadium, taken from open end of Horseshoe."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #193, 1929 May 3 (Box 3, Print WC193)
    From back of photo: "View showing campus front of Medical School."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #194, 1929 May 3 (Box 3, Print WC194)
    From back of photo: "View taken from Main Quadrangle showing front of Library Building and part of Union Building at extreme left of picture."
  - West Campus Progress Picture #195, 1929 May 3 (Box 3, Print WC195)